let questions = [{
  numb: 1,
  answer: "A) Non-coding regulatory RNA",
  question: "All of the following are part of functional non -protein coding sequences except?",
  options:[
     "A) Non-coding regulatory RNA",
     "B) Promoter and Enhancer region",
     "C) Exons",
     "D) Centromere"
  ]
 },

 {
  numb: 2,
  answer: "D) Chemically mediated endothelial contraction is usually reversible.",
  question: "Concerning vascular leakage with acute inflammation",
  options:[
     "A) Endothelial cell contraction preferentially occurs in arterioles 20-60 µm in diameter.",
     "B) Tumour necrosis factor (TNF) affects leakage by direct endothelial cell necrosis.",
     "C) Immediate sustained response is due to widening of intercellular gaps.",
     "D) Chemically mediated endothelial contraction is usually reversible."
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 3,
  answer: "A) The cytoskeletal and junctional retraction mechanism is mediated by the complement system",
  question: "Regarding the cellular mechanisms of vascular leakage, which of the following is INCORRECT",
  options:[
    "A) The cytoskeletal and junctional retraction mechanism is mediated by the complement system",
    "B) The immediate transient response only occurs in venules of 20-60 µm diameter.",
    "C) Sunburn can cause a delayed and prolonged vascular leakage.",
    "D) The most common mechanism for increased vascular permeability is endothelial contraction"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 4,
  answer: "D) All of the above.",
  question: "Cell adhesion molecules",
  options:[
    "A) Includes selectins.",
    "B) Assist in white cell pavementing.",
    "C) Involve endothelium.",
    "D) All of the above."
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 5,
  answer: "A) The selectins found only on endothelial cells.",
  question: "Leukocyte adhesion with transmigration involves all of the following EXCEPT",
  options:[
    "A) The selectins found only on endothelial cells.",
    "B) Interaction of integrins with immunoglobulin found on endothelial cells.",
    "C) ICAM-1 and VCAM-1 adhesive molecules on the endothelial cells.",
    "D) Neutrophils in the first 6-24 hours of acute inflammation."
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 6,
  answer: "C) Chemotaxis.",
  question: "The directional movement of a cell or organism in response to a chemical gradient is best called",
  options:[
    "A) Diapedesis.",
    "B) Emigration.",
    "C) Chemotaxis.",
    "D) Margination."
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 7,
  answer: "D) Bradykinin",
  question: "The chemical mediator NOT responsible for chemotaxis is?",
  options:[
    "A) C5a",
    "B) Cytokines",
    "C) LTB4",
    "D) Bradykinin"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 8,
  answer: "C) Causing venular endothelial contraction.",
  question: "Histamine exerts its effect during inflammation by",
  options:[
    "A) Constriction of large arteries.",
    "B) Acting on H2 receptors on mast cells.",
    "C) Causing venular endothelial contraction.",
    "D) Vasoconstriction of post capillary sphincters."
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 9,
  answer: "B) Directly converts C5 to C5a.",
  question: "About Kallikrein.",
  options:[
    "A) Negatively inhibits activation of Hageman Factor.",
    "B) Directly converts C5 to C5a.",
    "C) Is inactivated by kininase.",
    "D) All of the above."
  ]
 },
{
  numb: 10,
  answer: "A) Moose",
  question: "Giardia Lamblia may be spread by the faecal-oral route to people from all of the following EXCEPT",
  options:[
    "A) Moose",
    "B) Beavers",
    "C) People",
    "D) Cats"
  ]
 },

];